Guide to the Sunset Magazine Records M2065
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Photograph files
  - Slides, transparencies, and memo, 1987-12 (Box 376, Folder 7)
  - 12-87-001 to 12-87-050, 1987-12 (Box 377, Folder 1)
  - 12-87-051 to 12-87-105, 1987-12 (Box 377, Folder 2)
  - 12-87-106 to 12-87-160, 1987-12 (Box 377, Folder 3)
  - 12-87-161 to 12-87-200, 1987-12 (Box 377, Folder 4)
  - 12-87-201 to 12-87-243, 1987-12 (Box 377, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1988-01 (Box 377, Folder 6)
  - January 1988 Central magazine (Box 377, Folder 7)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memo, 1988-01 (Box 377, Folder 8)
  - 1-88-001 to 1-88-050, 1988-01 (Box 378, Folder 1)
  - 1-88-051 to 1-88-102, 1988-01 (Box 378, Folder 2)
  - 1-88-103 to 1-88-150, 1988-01 (Box 378, Folder 3)
  - 1-88-151 to 1-88-203, 1988-01 (Box 378, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1988-02 (Box 378, Folder 5)
  - February 1988 Central magazine (Box 378, Folder 6)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memo, 1988-02 (Box 378, Folder 7)
  - 2-88-001 to 2-88-050, 1988-02 (Box 379, Folder 1)
  - 2-88-051 to 2-88-100, 1988-02 (Box 379, Folder 2)
  - 2-88-101 to 2-88-150, 1988-02 (Box 379, Folder 3)
  - 2-88-151 to 2-88-190, 1988-02 (Box 379, Folder 4)
  - 2-88-191 to 2-88-233, 1988-02 (Box 379, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1988-02 (Box 379, Folder 6)
  - March 1988 Central magazine (Box 379, Folder 7)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1988-02 (Box 379, Folder 8)
  - 3-88-001 to 3-88-060, 1988-03 (Box 380, Folder 1)
  - 3-88-061 to 3-88-120, 1988-03 (Box 380, Folder 2)
  - 3-88-121 to 3-88-170, 1988-03 (Box 380, Folder 3)
  - 3-88-171 to 3-88-210, 1988-03 (Box 380, Folder 4)
  - 3-88-211 to 3-88-252, 1988-03 (Box 380, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1988-04 (Box 380, Folder 6)
  - April 1988 Central magazine, 1988-04 (Box 380, Folder 7)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1988-04 (Box 381, Folder 1)
  - 4-88-001 to 4-88-050, 1988-04 (Box 381, Folder 2)
  - 4-88-051 to 4-88-100, 1988-04 (Box 381, Folder 3)
  - 4-88-101 to 4-88-150, 1988-04 (Box 381, Folder 4)
  - 4-88-151 to 4-88-200, 1988-04 (Box 381, Folder 5)
  - 4-88-201 to 4-88-250, 1988-04 (Box 381, Folder 6)
  - 4-88-251 to 4-88-309, 1988-04 (Box 382, Folder 1)
  - Clippings,South, North, and Desert, 1988-04 (Box 382, Folder 2)
  - May 1988 Central magazine (Box 382, Folder 3)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1988-05 (Box 382, Folder 4)
  - 5-85-000 to 5-88-050, 1988-05 (Box 382, Folder 5)
  - 5-88-051 to 5-88-100, 1988-05 (Box 382, Folder 6)
  - 5-88-101 to 5-88-150, 1988-05 (Box 383, Folder 1)
  - 5-88-151 to 5-88-200, 1988-05 (Box 383, Folder 2)
  - 5-88-201 to 5-88-252, 1988-05 (Box 383, Folder 3)
  - 5-88-253 to 5-88-290, 1988-05 (Box 383, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1988-06 (Box 383, Folder 5)
  - June 1988 Central magazine (Box 383, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1988-06 (Box 383, Folder 7)
  - 6-88-003 to 6-88-050, 1988-06 (Box 383, Folder 8)
  - 6-88-051 to 6-88-100, 1988-06 (Box 384, Folder 1)
  - 6-88-101 to 6-88-150, 1988-06 (Box 384, Folder 2)
  - 6-88-151 to 6-88-200, 1988-06 (Box 384, Folder 3)
  - 6-88-201 to 6-88-260, 1988-06 (Box 384, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1988-07 (Box 384, Folder 5)
  - July 1988 Central magazine (Box 384, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1988-07 (Box 384, Folder 7)
  - 7-88-001 to 7-88-055, 1988-07 (Box 385, Folder 1)
  - 7-88-056 to 7-88-100, 1988-07 (Box 385, Folder 2)
  - 7-88-101 to 7-88-150, 1988-07 (Box 385, Folder 3)
  - 7-88-151 to 7-88-190, 1988-07 (Box 385, Folder 4)
  - 7-88-191 to 7-88-226, 1988-07 (Box 385, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1988-08 (Box 385, Folder 6)
  - August 1988 Central magazine (Box 385, Folder 7)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1988-08 (Box 385, Folder 8)
  - 8-88-001 to 8-88-040, 1988-08 (Box 386, Folder 1)
  - 8-88-041 to 8-88-090, 1988-08 (Box 386, Folder 2)
  - 8-88-091 to 8-88-135, 1988-08 (Box 386, Folder 3)
  - 8-88-136 to 8-88-186, 1988-08 (Box 386, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1988-09 (Box 386, Folder 5)
  - September 1988 Central magazine (Box 386, Folder 6)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1988-09 (Box 386, Folder 7)
  - 9-88-001 to 9-88-050, 1988-09 (Box 387, Folder 1)
  - 9-88-051 to 9-88-100, 1988-09 (Box 387, Folder 2)
  - 9-88-101 to 9-88-150, 1988-09 (Box 387, Folder 3)
  - 9-88-151 to 9-88-188, 1988-09 (Box 387, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1988-10 (Box 387, Folder 5)
  - October 1988 Central magazine (Box 387, Folder 6)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1988-10 (Box 387, Folder 7)
  - 10-88-001 to 10-88-051, 1988-10 (Box 388, Folder 1)
  - 10-88-052 to 10-88-100, 1988-10 (Box 388, Folder 2)
  - 10-88-101 to 10-88-151, 1988-10 (Box 388, Folder 3)
  - 10-88-152 to 10-88-200, 1988-10 (Box 388, Folder 4)
  - 10-88-201 to 10-88-250, 1988-10 (Box 388, Folder 5)
  - 10-88-251 to 10-88-307, 1988-10 (Box 388, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1988-11 (Box 389, Folder 1)
  - November 1988 Central magazine (Box 389, Folder 2)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1988-11 (Box 389, Folder 3)
  - 11-88-001 to 11-88-050, 1988-11 (Box 389, Folder 4)
  - 11-88-051 to 11-88-090, 1988-11 (Box 389, Folder 5)
  - 11-88-091 to 11-88-150, 1988-11 (Box 389, Folder 6)
  - 11-88-151 to 11-88-200, 1988-11 (Box 389, Folder 7)
  - 11-88-201 to 11-88-239, 1988-11 (Box 390, Folder 1)
  - 11-88-240 to 11-88-285, 1988-11 (Box 390, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1988-12 (Box 390, Folder 3)
  - December 1988 Central magazine (Box 390, Folder 4)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1988-12 (Box 390, Folder 5)
  - 12-88-001 to 12-88-045, 1988-12 (Box 390, Folder 6)
  - 12-88-046 to 12-88-080, 1988-12 (Box 390, Folder 7)
  - 12-88-081 to 12-88-105, 1988-12 (Box 390, Folder 8)
  - 12-88-106 to 12-88-155, 1988-12 (Box 391, Folder 1)
  - 12-88-156 to 12-88-206, 1988-12 (Box 391, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1989-01 (Box 391, Folder 3)
  - January 1989 Central magazine (Box 391, Folder 4)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1989-01 (Box 391, Folder 5)
  - 1-89-001 to 1-89-040, 1989-01 (Box 391, Folder 6)
  - 1-89-041 to 1-89-090, 1989-01 (Box 391, Folder 7)
  - 1-89-091 to 1-89-120, 1989-01 (Box 392, Folder 1)
  - 1-89-121 to 1-89-168, 1989-01 (Box 392, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1989-02 (Box 392, Folder 3)
  - February 1989 Central magazine (Box 392, Folder 4)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memo, 1989-02 (Box 392, Folder 5)
  - 2-89-001 to 2-89-049, 1989-02 (Box 392, Folder 6)
  - 2-89-050 to 2-89-102, 1989-02 (Box 392, Folder 7)
  - 2-89-103 to 2-89-144, 1989-02 (Box 393, Folder 1)
  - 2-89-145 to 2-89-186, 1989-02 (Box 393, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1989-03 (Box 393, Folder 3)
  - March 1989 Central magazine (Box 393, Folder 4)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1989-03 (Box 393, Folder 5)
  - 3-89-001 to 3-89-050, 1989-03 (Box 393, Folder 6)
  - 3-89-051 to 3-89-100, 1989-03 (Box 393, Folder 7)
  - 3-89-101 to 3-89-145, 1989-03 (Box 393, Folder 8)
  - 3-89-146 to 3-89-185, 1989-03 (Box 394, Folder 1)
  - Clippings,South, North, and Desert, 1989-04 (Box 394, Folder 2)
  - April 1989 Central magazine (Box 394, Folder 3)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1989-04 (Box 394, Folder 4)
  - 4-89-001 to 4-89-059, 1989-04 (Box 394, Folder 5)
  - 4-89-060 to 4-89-101, 1989-04 (Box 394, Folder 6)
  - 4-89-102 to 4-89-150, 1989-04 (Box 394, Folder 7)
  - 4-89-151 to 4-89-201, 1989-04 (Box 394, Folder 8)
  - 4-89-202 to 4-89-250, 1989-04 (Box 395, Folder 1)
  - Clippings,South, North, and Desert, 1989-05 (Box 395, Folder 2)
  - May 1989 Central magazine (Box 395, Folder 3)
  - Slides, transparencies, and memos, 1989-05 (Box 395, Folder 4)
  - 5-89-001 to 5-89-050, 1989-05 (Box 395, Folder 5)
  - 5-89-051 to 5-89-098, 1989-05 (Box 395, Folder 6)
  - 5-89-099 to 5-89-150, 1989-05 (Box 395, Folder 7)
  - 5-89-151 to 5-89-200, 1989-05 (Box 396, Folder 1)
  - 5-89-201 to 5-89-250, 1989-05 (Box 396, Folder 2)
  - 5-89-251 to 5-89-285, 1989-05 (Box 396, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1989-06 (Box 396, Folder 4)
  - June 1989 Central magazine, 1989-06 (Box 396, Folder 5)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1989-06 (Box 396, Folder 6)
  - 6-89-001 to 6-89-056, 1989-06 (Box 396, Folder 7)
  - 6-89-057 to 6-89-100, 1989-06 (Box 397, Folder 1)
  - 6-89-101 to 6-89-155, 1989-06 (Box 397, Folder 2)
  - 6-89-156 to 6-89-215, 1989-06 (Box 397, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1989-07 (Box 397, Folder 4)
  - July 1989 Central magazine (Box 397, Folder 5)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1989-07 (Box 397, Folder 6)
  - 7-89-001 to 7-89-050, 1989-07 (Box 397, Folder 7)
  - 7-89-051 to 7-89-100, 1989-07 (Box 397, Folder 8)
  - 7-89-101 to 7-89-139, 1989-07 (Box 398, Folder 1)
  - 7-89-140 to 7-89-182, 1989-07 (Box 398, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1989-08 (Box 398, Folder 3)
  - August 1989 Central magazine (Box 398, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1989-08 (Box 398, Folder 5)
  - 8-89-001 to 8-89-050, 1989-08 (Box 398, Folder 6)
  - 8-89-051 to 8-89-100, 1989-08 (Box 398, Folder 7)
  - 8-89-101 to 8-89-149, 1989-08 (Box 398, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1989-09 (Box 399, Folder 1)
  - September 1989 Central magazine (Box 399, Folder 2)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1989-09 (Box 399, Folder 3)
  - 9-89-001 to 9-89-050, 1989-09 (Box 399, Folder 4)
  - 9-89-01 to 9-89-100, 1989-09 (Box 399, Folder 5)
  - 9-89-101 to 9-89-135, 1989-09 (Box 399, Folder 6)
  - 9-89-136 to 9-89-182, 1989-09 (Box 399, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1989-10 (Box 399, Folder 8)
  - October 1989 Central magazine (Box 400, Folder 1)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1989-10 (Box 400, Folder 2)
  - 10-89-001 to 10-89-100, 1989-10 (Box 400, Folder 3)
  - 10-89-041 to 10-89-100, 1989-10 (Box 400, Folder 4)
  - 10-89-101 to 10-89-150, 1989-10 (Box 400, Folder 5)
  - 10-89-151 to 10-89-207, 1989-10 (Box 400, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1989-10 (Box 400, Folder 7)
  - November 1989 Central magazine (Box 401, Folder 1)
  - Slides and Clippings, 1989-11 (Box 401, Folder 2)
  - 11-89-001 to 11-89-040, 1989-11 (Box 401, Folder 3)
  - 11-89-041 to 11-89-080, 1989-11 (Box 401, Folder 4)
  - 11-89-081 to 11-89-129, 1989-11 (Box 401, Folder 5)
  - 11-89-130 to 11-89-180, 1989-11 (Box 401, Folder 6)
  - 11-89-181 to 11-89-236, 1989-11 (Box 401, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1989-11 (Box 402, Folder 1)
  - December 1989 Central magazine (Box 402, Folder 2)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1989-12 (Box 402, Folder 3)
  - 12-89-001 to 12-89-040, 1989-12 (Box 402, Folder 4)
  - 12-89-041 to 12-89-081, 1989-12 (Box 402, Folder 5)
  - 12-89-082 to 12-89-133, 1989-12 (Box 402, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1990-01 (Box 402, Folder 7)
  - January 1990 Central magazine (Box 402, Folder 8)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1990-01 (Box 402, Folder 9)
  - 1-90-001 to 1-90-040, 1990-01 (Box 403, Folder 1)
  - 1-90-041 to 1-90-100, 1990-01 (Box 403, Folder 2)
  - 1-90-101 to 1-90-137, 1990-01 (Box 403, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1990-02 (Box 403, Folder 4)
  - February 1990 Central magazine (Box 403, Folder 5)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1990-02 (Box 403, Folder 6)
  - 2-90-001 to 2-90-050, 1990-02 (Box 403, Folder 7)
  - 2-90-051 to 2-90-100, 1990-02 (Box 403, Folder 8)
  - 2-90-101 to 2-90-152, 1990-02 (Box 404, Folder 1)
  - Clippings,South, North, and Desert, 1990-03 (Box 404, Folder 2)
  - March 1990 Central magazine (Box 404, Folder 3)
  - Slides, and transparencies, 1990-03 (Box 404, Folder 4)
  - 3-90-001 to 3-90-051, 1990-03 (Box 404, Folder 5)
  - 3-90-052 to 3-90-091, 1990-03 (Box 404, Folder 6)
  - 3-90-091 to 3-90-140, 1990-03 (Box 404, Folder 7)
  - 3-90-141 to 3-90-192, 1990-03 (Box 405, Folder 1)
  - Clippings,South, North, and Desert, 1990-04 (Box 405, Folder 2)
  - April 1990 Central magazine (Box 405, Folder 3)
  - Slides, and transparencies, 1990-04 (Box 405, Folder 4)
  - 4-90-001 to 4-90-049, 1990-04 (Box 405, Folder 5)
  - 4-90-050 to 4-90-091, 1990-04 (Box 405, Folder 6)
  - 4-90-091 to 4-90-130, 1990-04 (Box 405, Folder 7)
  - 4-90-131 to 4-90-185, 1990-04 (Box 405, Folder 8)
  - 4-90-186 to 4-9-243, 1990-04 (Box 406, Folder 1)
  - Clippings,South, North, and Desert, 1990-05 (Box 406, Folder 2)
  - May 1990 Central magazine (Box 406, Folder 3)
  - Slides, and transparencies, 1990-05 (Box 406, Folder 4)
  - 5-90-001 to 5-90-045, 1990-05 (Box 406, Folder 5)
  - 5-90-046 to 5-90-101, 1990-05 (Box 406, Folder 6)
  - 5-90-102 to 5-90-175, 1990-05 (Box 406, Folder 7)
  - 5-90-176 to 5-90-230, 1990-05 (Box 407, Folder 1)
  - 5-90-231 to 5-90-278, 1990-05 (Box 407, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1990-05 (Box 407, Folder 3)
  - June 1990 Central magazine (Box 407, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1990-06 (Box 407, Folder 5)
  - 6-90-001 to 6-90-045, 1990-06 (Box 407, Folder 6)
  - 6-90-046 to 6-90-080, 1990-06 (Box 407, Folder 7)
  - 6-90-081 to 6-90-130, 1990-06 (Box 408, Folder 1)
  - 6-90-131 to 6-90-181, 1990-06 (Box 408, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South, North, and Desert, 1990-07 (Box 408, Folder 3)
  - July 1990 Central magazine (Box 408, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1990-07 (Box 408, Folder 5)
  - 7-90-001 to 7-90-045, 1990-07 (Box 408, Folder 6)
  - 7-90-046 to 7-90-095, 1990-07 (Box 408, Folder 7)
  - 7-90-096 to 7-90-140, 1990-07 (Box 409, Folder 1)
  - 7-90-141 to 7-90-185, 1990-07 (Box 409, Folder 2)
  - August 1990 Central magazine (Box 409, Folder 3)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1990-08 (Box 409, Folder 4)
  - 8-90-001 to 8-90-030, 1990-08 (Box 409, Folder 5)
  - 8-90-031 to 8-90-060, 1990-08 (Box 409, Folder 6)
  - 8-90-160 to 8-90-090, 1990-08 (Box 409, Folder 7)
  - 8-90-091 to 8-90-107, 1990-08 (Box 409, Folder 8)
  - 8-90-A1 to 8-90-A5, 1990-08 (Box 410, Folder 1)
  - 8-90-A13 to 8-90-A19, 1990-08 (Box 410, Folder 2)
  - September 1990 Central magazine (Box 410, Folder 3)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1990-09 (Box 410, Folder 4)
  - 9-90-001 to 9-90-015, 1990-09 (Box 410, Folder 5)
  - 9-90-016 to 9-90-040, 1990-09 (Box 410, Folder 6)
  - 9-90-041 to 9-90-060, 1990-09 (Box 410, Folder 7)
  - 9-90-061 to 9-90-085, 1990-09 (Box 411, Folder 1)
  - 9-90-86 to 9-90-104, 1990-09 (Box 411, Folder 2)
  - October 1990 Central magazine (Box 411, Folder 3)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1990-10 (Box 411, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies "Inside the Western Home", 1990-10 (Box 411, Folder 5)
  - 10-90-001 to 10-90-025, 1990-10 (Box 411, Folder 6)
  - 10-90-026 to 10-90-052, 1990-10 (Box 411, Folder 7)
  - November 1990 Central magazine (Box 412, Folder 1)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1990-11 (Box 412, Folder 2)
  - 11-90-001 to 11-90-020, 1990-11 (Box 412, Folder 3)
  - 11-90-021 to 11-90-040, 1990-11 (Box 412, Folder 4)
  - 11-90-041 to 11-90-060, 1990-11 (Box 412, Folder 5)
  - 11-90-061 to 11-90-086, 1990-11 (Box 412, Folder 6)
  - December 1990 Central magazine (Box 412, Folder 7)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1990-12 (Box 413, Folder 1)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1990-12 (Box 413, Folder 2)
  - 12-90-001 to 12-90-027, 1990-12 (Box 413, Folder 3)
  - January 1991 Central magazine (Box 413, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1991-01 (Box 413, Folder 5)
  - 1-91-001 to 1-91-018, 1991-01 (Box 413, Folder 6)
  - February 1991 Central magazine (Box 413, Folder 7)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1991-02 (Box 414, Folder 1)
  - 2-91-001 to 2-91-029, 1991-02 (Box 414, Folder 2)
  - March 1991 Central magazine (Box 414, Folder 3)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1991-03 (Box 414, Folder 4)
  - 3-91-001 to 3-91-044, 1991-03 (Box 414, Folder 5)
  - April 1991 Central magazine (Box 414, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1991-04 (Box 414, Folder 7)
  - 4-91-001 to 4-91-024, 1991-04 (Box 415, Folder 1)
  - May 1991 Central magazine (Box 415, Folder 2)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1991-05 (Box 415, Folder 3)
  - 5-91-001 to 5-91-031, 1991-05 (Box 415, Folder 4)
  - June 1991 Central magazine (Box 415, Folder 5)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1991-06 (Box 415, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1991-06 (Box 415, Folder 7)
  - July 1991 Central magazine (Box 416, Folder 1)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1991-07 (Box 416, Folder 2)
  - August 1991 Central magazine (Box 416, Folder 3)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1991-08 (Box 416, Folder 4)
  - September 1991 Central magazine (Box 416, Folder 5)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1991-09 (Box 416, Folder 6)
  - October 1991 Central magazine (Box 416, Folder 7)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1991-10 (Box 416, Folder 8)
  - November 1991 Central magazine (Box 417, Folder 1)
  - 11-91-243 to 11-91-249, 1991-11 (Box 417, Folder 2)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1991-11 (Box 417, Folder 3)
  - December 1991 Central magazine (Box 417, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1991-12 (Box 417, Folder 5)
  - January 1992 Central magazine (Box 417, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1992-01 (Box 417, Folder 7)
  - February 1992 Central magazine (Box 417, Folder 8)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1992-02 (Box 418, Folder 1)
  - March 1992 Central magazine (Box 418, Folder 2)
  - Slides and transprencies, 1992-03 (Box 418, Folder 3)
  - April 1992 Central magazine (Box 418, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1992-04 (Box 418, Folder 5)
  - May 1992 Central magazine (Box 418, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1992-05 (Box 418, Folder 7)
  - June 1992 Central magazine (Box 418, Folder 8)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1992-06 (Box 419, Folder 1)
  - July 1992 Central magazine (Box 419, Folder 2)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1992-07 (Box 419, Folder 3)
  - August 1992 Central magazine (Box 419, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1992-08 (Box 419, Folder 5)
  - September 1992 Central magazine (Box 419, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1992-09 (Box 419, Folder 7)
  - October 1992 Central magazine (Box 419, Folder 8)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1992-10 (Box 419, Folder 9)
  - November 1992 Central magazine (Box 419, Folder 10)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1992-11 (Box 420, Folder 1)
  - December 1992 Central magazine (Box 420, Folder 2)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1992-12 (Box 420, Folder 3)
  - January 1993 Central magazine (Box 420, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1993-01 (Box 420, Folder 5)
  - February 1993 Central magazine (Box 420, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1993-02 (Box 420, Folder 7)
  - March 1993 Central magazine (Box 420, Folder 8)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1993-03 (Box 420, Folder 9)
  - April 1993 Central magazine (Box 420, Folder 10)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1993-04 (Box 420, Folder 11)
  - Spring/Summer Best of West 1993 (Box 421, Folder 1)
  - Spring/Summer Garden Guide 1993 (Box 421, Folder 2)
  - Spring/Summer 1993 Best of West transparencies (Box 421, Folder 3)
  - May 1993 Central magazine (Box 421, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1993-05 (Box 421, Folder 5)
  - June 1993 Central magazine (Box 421, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1993-06 (Box 421, Folder 7)
  - July 1993 Central magazine (Box 421, Folder 8)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1993-07 (Box 421, Folder 9)
  - August 1993 Central magazine (Box 421, Folder 10)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1993-08 (Box 421, Folder 11)
  - September 1993 Central magazine (Box 422, Folder 1)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1993-09 (Box 422, Folder 2)
  - October 1993 Central magazine (Box 422, Folder 3)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1993-10 (Box 422, Folder 4)
  - November 1993 Central magazine (Box 422, Folder 5)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1993-11 (Box 422, Folder 6)
  - December 1993 Central magazine (Box 422, Folder 7)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1993-12 (Box 422, Folder 8)
  - January 1994 Central magazine (Box 422, Folder 9)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1994-01 (Box 423, Folder 1)
  - February 1994 Central magazine (Box 423, Folder 2)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1994-02 (Box 423, Folder 3)
  - March 1994 Central magazine (Box 423, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1994-03 (Box 423, Folder 5)
  - April 1994 Central magazine (Box 423, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1994-04 (Box 423, Folder 7)
  - May 1994 Central magazine (Box 423, Folder 8)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1994-05 (Box 423, Folder 9)
  - June 1994 Central magazine (Box 423, Folder 10)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1994-06 (Box 423, Folder 11)
  - July 1994 Central magazine (Box 424, Folder 1)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1994-07 (Box 424, Folder 2)
  - August 1994 Central magazine (Box 424, Folder 3)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1994-08 (Box 424, Folder 4)
  - September 1994 Central magazine (Box 424, Folder 5)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1994-09 (Box 424, Folder 6)
  - October 1994 Central magazine (Box 424, Folder 7)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1994-10 (Box 424, Folder 8)
  - Spring - Summer 1994 Garden Guide (Box 424, Folder 9)
  - Fall - Winter 1994 Garden Guide (Box 424, Folder 10)
  - Fall - Winter 1994 Slides and transparencies (Box 424, Folder 11)
  - November 1994 Central magazine (Box 424, Folder 12)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1994-11 (Box 425, Folder 1)
  - December 1994 Central magazine (Box 425, Folder 2)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1994-12 (Box 425, Folder 3)
  - January 1995 Central magazine (Box 425, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1995-01 (Box 425, Folder 5)
  - February 1995 Central magazine (Box 425, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1995-02 (Box 425, Folder 7)
  - March 1995 Central magazine (Box 425, Folder 8)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1995-03 (Box 425, Folder 9)
  - April 1995 Central magazine (Box 425, Folder 10)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1995-034 (Box 425, Folder 11)
  - Spring - Summer 1995 Garden Guide Slides and transparencies (Box 425, Folder 12)
  - May 1995 Central magazine (Box 425, Folder 13)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1995-05 (Box 425, Folder 14)
  - June 1995 Central magazine (Box 426, Folder 1)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1995-06 (Box 426, Folder 2)
  - Spring - Summer 1995 Garden Guide magazine (Box 426, Folder 3)
  - July 1995 Central magazine (Box 426, Folder 4)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1995-07 (Box 426, Folder 5)
  - August 1995 Central magazine (Box 426, Folder 6)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1995-08 (Box 426, Folder 7)
  - September 1995 Central magazine (Box 426, Folder 8)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1995-09 (Box 426, Folder 9)
  - October 1995 Central magazine (Box 426, Folder 10)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1995-10 (Box 426, Folder 11)
  - November 1995 Central magazine (Box 426, Folder 12)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1995-11 (Box 426, Folder 13)
  - December 1995 Central magazine (Box 426, Folder 14)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1995-12 (Box 426, Folder 15)
  - January 1996 Central magazine (Box 427, Folder 1)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1996-01 (Box 427, Folder 2)
  - February 1996 Central magazine (Box 427, Folder 3)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1996-02 (Box 427, Folder 4)
  - March 1996 Central magazine (Box 427, Folder 5)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1996-03 (Box 427, Folder 6)
  - April 1996 Central magazine (Box 427, Folder 7)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1996-04 (Box 427, Folder 8)
  - Spring - Summer 1996 Central magazine (Box 427, Folder 9)
  - Spring - Summer 1996 Slides and transparencies (Box 427, Folder 10)
  - May 1996 Central magazine (Box 427, Folder 11)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1996-05 (Box 427, Folder 12)
  - June 1996 Central magazine (Box 427, Folder 13)
  - Slides and transparencies, 1996-06 (Box 427, Folder 14)
  - July 1996 Central magazine (Box 427, Folder 15)